shadestation.co.uk 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy

Shade Ltd understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of all of our customers and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described here, and in a way that is consistent with our obligations and your rights under the law. This Customer Privacy Policy explains how Shade Ltd (including our employees) will use any personal information that we collect from you as part of the processing of orders with Shade Ltd Please ensure you have read this Customer Privacy Policy carefully, in particular the section detailing your rights as a data subject in relation to the personal information that we collect about you. 

**1\. Who we are**

Shade Ltd (‘we or ‘us) are a data controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Act 2018, (i.e. we are responsible for, and control the processing of, your personal information). 

**2\. What information we collect about you**

Personal information we collect from you and how we collect it 

  * Name
  * Addresses
  * Phone numbers
  * Email addresses

We collect this personal information when you: 

  * Place an order on our website

**3\. How we will use the information about you**

We use your personal information in a number of different ways: 

  * For administration and management purposes
  * For the purpose of facilitating the supply of goods.
  * To deal with customer complaints or queries

**4\. How long we will store your information**

We’ll hold on to your information unless you specifically request that we remove it. This allows us address any warranty issues. 

**5\. Your rights over your information**

Data subjects have many rights over their personal information and how it is used. The following rights are available to data subjects (depending on how we collect their personal data): 

  * Right to be informed about what we do with personal data 
  * Right to access personal data 
  * Right to correct personal data 
  * Right to object to, or restrict, the use of personal data (in some circumstances) 
  * Right to delete personal data 
  * Right to stop direct marketing messages 
  * Right to portability of personal data 

To the extent you, as a data subject, wish to exercise any of these rights, please write to us at info@shadestation.co.uk 

**Consent**   
Where Shade Ltd is using your personal information based on your express consent to this, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.   
To withdraw your consent please write to info@shadestation.co.uk 

**Complain to the Regulator**   
You have the right to lodge a complaint with your relevant regulatory authority. In the UK this is the Information Commissioners Office and in the Republic of Ireland this is the Office of the Data Protection Commissioner. 

**6\. Marketing**

If you have given us your contact details, we may use these (in accordance with any preferences you have expressed) to send you marketing messages by post or email to detail offers or events which we think may be of interest. As part of our relationship Shade Ltd considers that it has a legitimate interest to send you these messages unless you have asked for us not to do this. 

You can stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time. You can do this by writing to us at info@shadestation.co.uk or unsubscribing on the link at the bottom of all emails. 

**7\. Changes to our Customer Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, to reflect how we are processing your personal information. If we make significant changes, we will make that clear on the Shade Ltd websites 

**8\. How to contact us**

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions about our Customer Privacy policy or the personal data we hold about you. 

You can contact us by email: [info@shadestation.co.uk](https://www.shadestation.co.uk/info@shadestation.co.uk)

By phone: 0344 848 7878
